<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyWifiHeatmap</string>
    <string name="permission_denied_title">Permission Missing</string>
    <string name="quit">Exit App</string>
    <string name="continue_txt">Continue</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="fine_location_denied">The Location permission is missing.\n\n
        This permission is used to easily find your location on the map, it does not need to be turned on.\n\n
        To grant this permission click on Settings, then Permissions and turn the Location permission on.
        Then click back twice to return to the app</string>

    <string name="storage_location_denied">The Storage permission is missing.\n\n
        This permission is used to save images to your SD Card, it does not need to be turned on.\n\n
        To grant this permission click on Settings, then Permissions and turn the Storage permission on.
        Then click back twice to return to the app</string>

    <string name="defualt_text">This is the default text</string>
    <string name="hit_next">Hit the next button to continue to next steps.</string>
    <string name="do_not_show">Show helpful tips.</string>

    <!-- map info screen strings -->
    <string name="map_instructions_header">Selecting a Location</string>
    <string name="map_instructions_body">
        Search a location or use your own to locate the building of interest.\n\n
        Zoom, pan, and rotate to get building as large as possible while still keeping the
        boundaries on screen.
    </string>

    <!-- zoom strings -->
    <string name="zoom_dialog_title">Adjust zoom?</string>
    <string name="zoom_dialog_body">Try to get the building of interest as large as possible within
        the screen bounds.</string>
    <string name="zoom_dialog_confirm">Zoom</string>
    <string name="zoom_dialog_deny">Continue</string>
    <!-- zoom info strings -->
    <string name="zoom_instructions_header">Zooming on a Location</string>
    <string name="zoom_instructions_body">
        This app works best when the building of interest is as large as possible on your device screen.\n\n
        Zoom and pan to adjust your building as large as possible within the screen bounds.
    </string>

    <!-- boundry info screen strings -->
    <!-- I didn't know how to spell boundary when I created these values and I'm way too lazy to change everything -->
    <string name="boundry_instructions_header">Creating a Boundary</string>
    <string name="boundry_instructions_body">
        Place and drag your finger to outline the building of interest.\n\n
        Use the undo button in the top right to undo the latest drawn line.
    </string>

    <!-- heatmap info screen strings -->
    <string name="heatmap_instructions_header">Creating a Heatmap</string>
    <string name="heatmap_instructions_body">
        As you walk through the building of interest, hold your finger down on the device screen in
        your approximate location.\n\n
        Colors will be drawn underneath your finger showing the current wifi strength.\n
        Red depicts a strong signal, while blue depicts a weak signal.
    </string>

</resources>
